rw-co.com 2009-07-22

# RW&CO. Privacy Policy

****

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to the RW&CO. web site (the “Site “). At RW&CO., we value our customers and respect your privacy. We collect information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and special promotions. RW&CO. recognizes that it must maintain and use your personal information responsibly. We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and security, and to advise you about the possible uses we will make of personal information collected during your visit to our Site.

**What Information is Collected on our Web Site?**

Every time you visit the Site, the following non-personally identifiable information is automatically obtained and compiled: the internet protocol (IP) address, the domain name registry information associated with the IP address, your internet browser, operating system and hardware platform, the date and time of your visit, the name and address (URL) of the web page you viewed immediately prior to accessing the current page, your entire query (if any) that was entered into a search engine which led you to the current site and any other " click stream " data. This information is stored in our log files. Occasionally, if your browser is not configured to prevent disclosure of such information, the following information may also be revealed: your name, e-mail address, home and work addresses, telephone and fax numbers and any plain text commentary. Additionally, the complete record of your actions at the web site including all pages visited, time spent at each page, the information sent or received and the names of all files uploaded or downloaded are available. This tracking information may be compiled by us in the aggregate and made available to third parties primarily to identify demographic data regarding our customers. 

It is important to note that IP addresses do not necessarily reveal the identity of an individual visitor. Since most individuals connect through an internet service provider at home, the IP address would identify the internet service provider and not that actual person. Users should refer to these specific instructions accompanying their browsers to ensure that personal information is not automatically being provided without their agreement. 

**How Is Your Personal Information Used?**

In order to better serve you, we may combine information you give us on-line, in our stores or through print media, with information about your product interests and purchases. We may also combine these with readily available demographic information in order to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us and to enable us to communicate with you, by e-mail or otherwise, about our products, promotions, contests or related third party products or services which we believe may be of interest to you. We gather this information in order to: i) maintain contact with you and provide you with ongoing personalized service; ii) better understand and respond to your needs; and iii) develop, improve and market products and services. We also use this information to measure interest in the various areas of our Site, to ensure that links on the Site facilitate easy navigation and to help make the Site more interesting and informative. Any personal information that we disclose to third parties is done in the aggregate on a non-personally identifiable basis and is used primarily to identify demographic data regarding our customers.

Customers electing to register to join the reitmans.com community are asked to provide personal information prior to acquiring access to the community. Occasionally, we may also collect information volunteered by the customer, such as survey information or contest entries. 

By accessing this Site, you hereby agree to all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to receive marketing or promotional communication in electronic, printed or verbal format, please inform us in writing or by e-mail at the addresses found below.

**What Are "Cookies" and How Do We Use Cookies On Our Web Site?**

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site stores on your computer's hard drive or in random access memory when you are viewing the web site. A cookie may contain information such as a unique user ID that can be used to track the pages of the web site you've visited, login or registration information and user preferences. In certain cases, this information is only kept during the session and is deleted when you close your browser. In other cases, the information is stored on your hard drive and, upon your next visit to the web site, the cookies are used to recall such information. Cookies identify your computer or browser and do not contain any personally identifiable information. 

We use cookies in order to improve your on-line experience. Your cookies help us keep track of your interests and, if you are a registered customer, your cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to the Site. If you register on our Site, your cookies also help us to monitor and maintain information about your use of our Site. If you have not registered with us, your cookies may be used in order to monitor and maintain non-personally identifiable information about your use of our Site. 

You can choose either to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to turn off all cookies. This is done through your browser settings. However, if you disable the cookie function, your experience on the Site might be limited as, amongst other things, we will not recognize you as a past visitor or a registered user. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on our Site so that you can be updated as to what information we gather, how that information may be used and whether (and how) it may be disclosed to any third parties. 

**Other Terms**

Your use of this Site is subject to our Terms of Use. 

**Limitation Of Liability**

In no event, in regard to this Site or any other hyperlinked web site, will Reitmans be liable to you or anyone else for any damages or injury whatsoever (including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, exemplary or punitive damages) arising out of or in connection with your use or inability to use the Site and, without limitation, any lost profits, business interruption, loss of programs or other data on your information handling system or otherwise, even if we are expressly advised of the possibility of such damages. 

Your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using and accessing this Site. To the extent that the jurisdiction to which you are subject does not allow any part of such limitation, such part does not apply to you. 

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@rw-co.com](mailto:info@rw-co.com), and we will be pleased to respond to your inquiry promptly. You may also contact us in writing at: 

Reitmans ( Canada ) Limited/RW&CO. Division  
250 Sauvé Street West  
Montréal, Québec  
H3L 1Z2 

Attention: Marketing, RW&CO. Division 

RW&CO. will remove any personal information from our database pursuant to a written request from you. Please e-mail such request to us, identifying your full name and password and please type "remove registrant" in the subject line of your email.
